

No-7, Basaweshwara Nilaya, 5th Cross, 2nd Main, Brindavan Nagar, Bangalore, India

🛘 (+91) 8123089095 | 🗷 vikrant.biswas@gmail.com | 🏕 vikrant.pages.dev | 🖸 windlessstorm | 🛅 vikrantb

Summary.

Currently working as a Software Engineer at Mitel Networks. 6+ years of experience specializing in Full Stack Development, Test Automation, and System Administration. I am passionate about finding effective solutions to difficult problems and am committed to staying current with the latest technologies and tools.

Skills

DevOps AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins

Back-end Express, Django, REST API Front-end Angular, React, Vue, Hugo

Programming Node.js, Typescript, Python, Rust, C

Work Experience _____

Mitel Networks Co. Bangalore, India

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Aug. 2017 - Present

- Built real-time collaborative whiteboard solution for our meeting platform.
- Built automated test framework, tests and CI/CD pipeline on Jenkins using Python, Selenium, Typescript, NodeJs.

Endurance International Group

Bangalore, India

HOSTING PRODUCT ENGINEER

Dec. 2016 - Aug. 2017

· Pro-actively monitor product/services/site performance, uptime, availability and analyze logs/metrics and recommend/contribute to fixes.

iSOKE Technologies

Bangalore, India

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN May. 2016 - Aug. 2016 • Developed application to load test network appliances with simulated traffic of various L2, L3, and L4 network protocols.

· Developed auto-scaling large-scale network traffic simulator, used to simulate mutiple network topology and state.

Honors & Awards

Feb. 2022 Finalist, Mitel Global Shark Tank Oct. 2021 1st Place, Mitel India Hackathon Feb. 2021 4th Place, Mitel Global Shark Tank Oct. 2020 1st Place, Mitel India Hackathon

Global, Remote Bangalore, India

Global, Remote Bangalore, India

Education

MAKAUT (Maulana Abul Kalam Azad University of Technology)

Kolkata, India

B. TECH. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Aug. 2011 - Sept. 2015

· Participated in and won multiple coding competitions.

Extracurricular Activity

Advent of Code Bangalore, India

PARTICIPANT Dec. 2017/2018/2019/2022

- 2019: Tried to learn Rust from basics while solving all the puzzles.
- 2018: Tried to learn Go-lang from basics while solving all the puzzles.
- 2017: Had fun trying to do visualization for all the puzzle solutions in JavaScript

Hacktoberfest 2022 Bangalore, India

PARTICIPANT Oct 2022

• Wanted to start contributing to Rust projects. Had 3 successful PR's accepted.

VIKRANT BISWAS · RÉSUMÉ **DECEMBER 13, 2022**